By coding along with me in this intermediate Python workshop, you're going to learn how to use
object-oriented programming to organize your code. You're going to learn how to diagnose
problems in your Python programs by understanding exceptions and even writing your own.
We're going to work with new features in Python 3 that make Python easier than ever,
such as F strings. You're going to learn a little bit about generators, a Python feature that
allows you to loop over large data sets in a memory efficient way. You're also going to learn
about list comprehensions, dictionary comprehensions, and other advanced ways of looping Python.
Lastly, for the final exercise, you're going to learn how to use an interactive API and build a
web application efficiently using the Flask web framework to make a really cool site that let's
us filter GitHub repositories for a particular language by their number of stars. Taking a peek at
that final exercise, here we go. We can filter by languages, submit, and our little web app is going
to hit the GitHub search API and come back with results.